[music]
This is S Pack the Dream Social Challenge
2025 Indonesia Final.
[music]
We are committed to [music]
supporting students to not only
understand the concept of financial literacy, but
also be able to apply it in
[music] the form of real solutions that have a
positive impact on the community.
It can be seen that [music] from the junior high school level
they have thought about the concept of desires and
needs and how to implement the concept
in the future so that this [music] activity is
very good to continue to
be implemented.
First [music] place winner goes to.
[music]
Of course, we are all very happy and
grateful because our efforts during
[music] have resulted in us becoming champions
here.